<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SE7EN</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pilin_profile">PilinProfile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ben_profile">BenProfile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_robert_profile">RobertProfile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pilin">PilinActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mohamed">MohamedActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_soloman">SolomanActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_robert">RobertActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_solomon_profile">SolomonProfile</string>
    <string name="mission_statement">By efficiently leveraging time, skill and knowledge. SE7EN seeks to increase the needs of companies and organizations towards building sophisticated and robust mobile applications. </string>


    <string name="project1_ben">CTES</string>
    <string name="project2_ben">Bank-Teller</string>
    <string name="project3_ben">Mad-Libs</string>
    <string name="bio_ben">Hi I am Mohamed Ben I have a bachelor degree in Information Technology
I chose to learn Android Mobile app development because I really love to see my imagination come to life, my plans are to be Android Mobile app development because I really love to see my imagination come to life. I chose to learn to web development and intend to work at a tech company because a stimulating workspace is crucial in order to get more experience in the short term and grow my skill set and try new things and learn from the best. Above all, l enjoy wearing multiple hats. With this kind of skills, knowledge, and experience, I can build my own computing/IT consulting Solutions company within a 5-7 year time frame. In the very long-term, I hope to earn a Ph.D. in Computer Science.
</string>


    <string name="project1_sw">INSERT GITHUB PROJECT1 NAME HERE</string>
    <string name="project2_sw">INSERT GITHUB PROJECT2 NAME HERE</string>
    <string name="project3_sw">INSERT GITHUB PROJECT3 NAME HERE</string>
    <string name="bio_sw">INSERT BIO HERE</string>


    <string name="project1_rz">Choose-your-own-adventure Game</string>
    <string name="project2_rz">Bank Teller</string>
    <string name="project3_rz">Mad-Libs</string>
    <string name="bio_rz">Hi! My name is Robert. I have a background in Psychology but have always been fascinated by technology. I really like how it has been integrated into daily life and I want to become a mobile android developer because I want to make its usage more accessible to everyone. Also - I love languages and how it builds bridges. I want to apply the same concept to computer languages to build bridges between people and technology. I would like to eventually have an established career within the tech industry as a developer and product manager. On my spare time, I can often be found eating baby carrots and reading fun facts - for example: bananas are curved because they grow towards the sun.

Fun Fact about myself:
I love beaches but hate sand.
</string>


    <string name="project1_pc">Mad Libs</string>
    <string name="project2_pc">String Game|Java</string>
    <string name="project3_pc">DroidCafe-Codelab4.2</string>
    <string name="bio_pc">INSERT BIO HERE</string>


</resources>
